hi spring band and since ominous
嗨，春季乐队，因为不祥
we're going to go ahead and take a look
我们要去看看
at spring batch and particularly looking
在春季批，特别是外观
at spring batch before because I want to
在春季批次之前，因为我想
make sure we could cover some of the
确保我们可以涵盖一些
niceties that were proposed and already
已经提出并已经存在的细微之处
included in the first milestone for
包含在第一个里程碑中
spring back for that oh so we're going
为此反弹哦，所以我们要去
to take a look at a simple example here
在这里看一个简单的例子
today we're going to go ahead and go to
今天我们要继续前进
the facts demo
事实演示
starting with the SPG neutralizer as we
从SPG中和剂开始
always do I'm going to go ahead and use
我总是会继续使用
spring book 1.5 rc1 not because you need
春天书1.5 rc1不是因为你需要
to be 1.5 per se but because that'll
本身就是1.5，因为那会
give me the snapshot and mouse and
给我快照和鼠标，
repositories which then I can use to
然后我可以用来存储
draw the milestone for spring match
绘制春季比赛的里程碑
itself so it's used my sequel driver
本身，所以用了我的续集驱动程序
will use JDBC support here we'll use
在这里我们将使用JDBC支持
batch support as well and and that I
批处理支持以及我
think will do so go ahead and hit
认为会这样做，继续打击
generate then I'll give it some new
生成然后我给它一些新的
projects which all start a game generate
所有开始游戏的项目都会产生
a new one open this up in my IDE
一个新的在我的IDE中打开
so what we have here is a simple spoon
所以我们这里有一个简单的汤匙
root application as usual in order for
像往常一样root应用程序
us to work with spring batch we need
我们需要春季批处理
that opt in now we need to activate it
现在选择启用，我们需要激活它
so we say at normal batch processing and
所以我们说在正常的批处理中
this sense of the auto configuration is
这种自动配置的意义是
activated on a configuration which in
在以下配置中激活
turn sets up all of the spring batch
依次设置所有春季批
infrastructure because the spring batch
基础设施，因为春季批
is meant to run long-running jobs right
旨在正确运行长期运行的作业
from back to the way of modern batch
从回到现代批处理的方式
processes batch processes by their very
他们非常处理批处理
nature are long-running are staple and
大自然是永恒的主食和
so you have to keep that state summer
所以你必须保持夏天的状态
spring batch does that in the sequel
春季批处理在续集中做到这一点
database for you it will install all the
数据库为您将安装所有
requisite metadata samples for you if
为您提供必要的元数据样本
you want as well so it'll do that on
您也要这样，它将在
application startup which is why the
应用程序启动，这就是为什么
first thing that we need to do is that
我们需要做的第一件事是
the point to our data source so I'm
指向我们的数据源，所以我
going to go ahead and just copy the
要继续，只需复制
properties here that I've guarded that
我一直在保护的物业
ran around toss them and I will paste
到处扔他们，我将粘贴
that here there's my setup my local
这是我的本地设置
machine and the local historian among
机与当地历史学家之间
people instance and with that I'll have
人们实例，有了这个实例
a data source that might seek that a
可能会寻求
multiple data source of screen back from
从屏幕返回的多个数据源
those who connect you into configure now
那些将您连接到立即配置的人
swing batch is just as any other batch
摇摆批次与其他批次一样
processing system it's very similar to
处理系统非常类似于
the anything anything you may have
你可能拥有的任何东西
worked with in the past including sort
过去曾与包括
of more antiquated as mainframe kind of
更陈旧的大型机
technology like kick and COBOL and kick
踢，COBOL和踢等技术
so in that world there's very common
所以在那个世界上很普遍
jars and bracelet very common that sort
罐子和手镯很常见
of a domain knowledge that's required
所需的领域知识
understand and work with batch
了解并批量处理
processing which batch processing is
处理是哪个批处理
optimized for is dealing with lots of or
为处理大量或
large amounts of sequential data so in
大量的顺序数据
the world of that first thing you have
你拥有的第一件事的世界
this idea of a job an operator typically
作业者的这种想法通常
runs the job in our case swing boot will
在我们的情况下运行作业
run the job for us so it'll look for any
为我们负责这项工作，以便寻找
jobs in the spring application context
Spring应用程序上下文中的作业
when this Java process is started and
当此Java进程启动时，
then just run them you can explicitly
然后只要运行它们，您就可以显式
kick them off perhaps in your in
踢他们也许在你的
response to a an event like a web
响应网络等事件
request or a message arriving or
请求或消息到达或
something like that but the default
类似的东西，但默认
behavior with spring boot
弹簧靴的行为
auto-configuration is to run the job on
自动配置是在以下位置运行作业
applications
应用领域
then a job itself is made up of several
那么工作本身就是由几个
steps or stages each step takes data
步骤或阶段每个步骤都需要数据
from some sort of source reads it
从某种来源读取它
optionally then processes it and then
然后可选地对其进行处理，然后
writes it out so you you do this in as
写出来，所以你这样做
many successive steps as you need to to
您需要执行的许多连续步骤
arrive at a result so you might take
得到一个结果，所以你可能会采取
data from a file system and then and
来自文件系统的数据，然后
then put in a database test a basic
然后放入数据库测试一个基本
detail kind of processing right and then
详细的处理权然后
you might analyze that David Davies and
您可能会分析David Davies和
then process or result and then write
然后处理或结果然后写
that out to another file this is very
到另一个文件，这是非常
very common sort of batch processing and
非常常见的批处理
is using Hadoop or : cakes or anything
正在使用Hadoop或：cakes或其他任何东西
else like that you'll recognize the EM
否则你会认识到EM
the basic structure of a batch
批处理的基本结构
processing job so the first thing we
处理工作，所以我们第一件事
need to do here is to build a job I'm
这里需要做的是建立我的工作
going to build a job using the you know
打算用你知道的工作
Java configuration and the Java config
Java配置和Java配置
API so when you use the job builders
API，因此在您使用工作生成器时
Factory ABF and the job will have
工厂ABF和工作将有
multiple steps so build that using the
多个步骤，因此使用
steps of the factory SBF animal tell
工厂SBF动物的步骤告诉
spring batch to our created jobs called
春天批处理到我们创造的工作称为
ETL right and the child will have an
ETL权利，孩子将有一个
increment er unless to say a unique ID
er，除非说出唯一的ID
will be automatically assigned each job
将自动分配给每个作业
because remember by default by default
因为默认情况下默认记住
it's um it's going to turn to look at
嗯，它将转向看
the parameters that we use to kick off
我们开始使用的参数
the job and then use that as a way of
工作，然后将其用作一种方式
sort of assigning it a unique primary
为其分配一个唯一的主要对象
key so when the spring batch launches a
关键，这样当春季批启动时
job it looks at the parameters that go
工作它看去的参数
into that job and it is use that and
从事这项工作，并使用它和
store the invaders so if we then try to
储存入侵者，所以如果我们再尝试
run the same job with the same in but it
以相同的方式进行相同的工作，但是
looks like this is already running
看起来这已经在运行
you've already run it or it's already
您已经运行它或它已经
running we can't launch again so for our
运行我们无法再次启动，所以对于我们
purposes we're going in rating right now
目的是我们现在要进行评级
we'll make it just automatically ascribe
我们将使其自动归因
assign leather and the IDS on each one
在每一个上分配皮革和IDS
okay so the first step that we need to
好，所以我们需要的第一步
do is is to describe a step so I will
要做的是描述一个步骤，这样我会
say step s 1 equals SBS got six I'm
说步骤s 1等于SBS得到6我
going to say we want to read Justina
要说我们想读Justina
from the file and give us a file here
从文件中给我们一个文件
that
那
Pop's in that CSV it has names ages
该CSV的流行音乐名称年龄
Amina Isis we've got only two thousand
Amina Isis，我们只有两千
ten thousand records so the small file
万条记录，所以小文件
but it allow us to go back the beauty of
但它使我们可以追溯到
spring batches that is optimized for
弹簧批次已针对
large amounts of data so it's not going
大量的数据，所以它不会
to do anything naive right it's not
天真地做任何事不是
going to try and load it's not going to
尝试加载它不会
be a select all we've got the on a date
选择所有我们约会的对象
still that's tomorrow mr. Kersh through
仍然是明天先生。穿过克什
the ropes example here dancer and
这里的绳索示例舞者和
available anything even if you have a
即使你有一个可用的任何东西
million records to code the storage of a
百万条记录来编码一个
million records and code of for twenty
百万条记录和20条代码
good and level 16 batch has built-in
良好且内置16级级别
support for paralyzing and defining that
支持瘫痪和定义
work as well when badge has this notion
当徽章具有此概念时也可以正常工作
of as chunks whether it seems through
是否看起来像通过
the data it goes you know leave a buffer
你知道的数据留下缓冲
in a large bucket what is called a chunk
在一个大桶里叫做大块
and then it tries to write that chunk to
然后尝试将其写入
this to the writer in a read as much as
在给读者的阅读中
it can and write and read as much of the
它可以写和读尽可能多的
can then write we can tell it what size
然后可以写我们可以告诉它什么大小
chunks we want so we're going to call
我们想要的块，所以我们要调用
this file to saving for this file to GD
将此文件保存为GD
nice and when you tell us they want to
很好，当你告诉我们他们想
create a a application that that reads
创建一个读取的应用程序
data from our file system and turned it
来自我们文件系统的数据并将其打开
into a POJO of certain types on this
变成某些类型的POJO
case when i paid it for joke just called
当我为开玩笑而付了钱的情况下
person now it's using modern language
现在的人正在使用现代语言
like cotton or goofy or Scala or
例如棉花，高飞或Scala或
something like this then this is one
这样的东西然后这是一个
genius code generation that we're doing
我们正在做的天才代码生成
here is is not something you have to
这不是你必须要做的
worry about the for our purposes we're
为我们的目的而担心
just uh orgies in Java and I couldn't
只是Java中的狂欢，我做不到
use longer long blocks that would then
使用更长的长块，然后
just fine as well might be a little bit
也可以一点点
at equal to AB data and then just a
等于AB数据，然后
field and you have been done but
领域，您已经完成，但是
whatever we're fine so we have a field
无论我们如何都好，所以我们有一个领域
here and we're going to take the data
在这里，我们要获取数据
from the file come read it and turn it
从文件中读取并打开它
into records of type person and then
记录到类型人员的记录中，然后
write it out from records of that
从那个记录中写出来
person's to the file system such as
人的文件系统，例如
database so it on the input is personnel
数据库，所以它在输入上是人员
different because I'm going to say that
不一样，因为我要说的是
when a weed records rather write records
当杂草记录而写记录时
in terms of let's say 100 records their
假设有100条记录
time now
是时候了
again you want to fine-tune this this is
再次，你想微调这是
a a knob and the leaver for you just
一个旋钮和你的离开者
sort of playlists in order to arrive at
某种播放列表以便到达
the most of vacation systems the goal
大多数假期系统的目标
here is to not overwhelm your gather
这是不要压倒你的聚会
profit if you're reading a million
如果你读一百万，就赚钱
records it might be finding on 1,000
记录可能在1,000上找到的记录
records at a time another thing to
一次记录另一件事
consider when you simplify a chunk size
考虑何时简化块大小
is how many records are you willing to
您愿意记录多少条记录
to serve marked as incorrect and move to
标记为不正确并转到
the five write it the way that spring
五个人写那春天的样子
batch works is if it has different
批量工作是否不同
settings different things you can
设置不同的东西可以
configure in specifying what happens if
在指定发生什么情况时进行配置
a particular chunk of data fails to read
特定数据块无法读取
or parse or to do plot that's perfect if
或分析或进行绘图，如果
something goes wrong you know during
在发生错误时，您知道
records 999,000 to them you know all the
给他们记录999,000
way to the end example to the last
到最后的例子
million you want to stop and you want to
百万你想停下来，你想
fail the whole job or you want to scale
整个工作失败或您想要扩展
that chunk you want to just note that
您只想注意的那部分
particular uncle failed and then allow
特定的叔叔失败了，然后允许
the job to succeed right in general
一般而言，成功的工作
things that you have to take into mind
你要考虑的事情
when you describe and build a batch job
当您描述并建立批处理作业时
and thankfully it's easy to do that
幸运的是，这样做很容易
right so you can mark for example
对的，所以你可以标记例如
certain chunk is that if a certain chunk
某个块是如果某个块
failed by that you should just just you
失败了，你应该只是你
should be noted in the metadata tables
应该在元数据表中注明
and an operator can come along and
操作员可以过来
observe that so we're going to say chunk
观察，所以我们要说大块
of size 100 and then we need to tell it
大小为100，然后我们要告诉它
how to read the data so we are looking
如何读取数据，所以我们正在寻找
for an item leader of some sort of
对于某种形式的项目负责人
credit parameter here item leader okay
信用参数在这里项目负责人可以
Excel and we're going to also write the
Excel，我们还将编写
data so I'm going to use the item writer
数据，所以我将使用项目编写器
item
项目
writer of some sort so let's create that
某种作家，让我们来创建
as well
以及
okay and I'll build that now that's our
好的，我现在将其建立，这就是我们的
first job will tell Spring bash about it
第一份工作会告诉Spring bash
and we've got a first step there we need
我们已经迈出了第一步
to actually describe these item design
实际描述这些项目设计
Winer sound so let's go ahead and define
Winer的声音，让我们继续进行定义
a few beans now this is one of the my
现在有几个豆是我的之一
speech doesn't where we get to look at
演讲不是我们要去看的地方
for a nice features and
具有不错的功能
spring batch for Dino the builders to
Dino建筑商的春季批
see spring batch has a very rich
看春批有很丰富
collection of item readers and einer
项目阅读器和特征的集合
meiner and you know they do all sorts of
迈纳，你知道他们做各种各样的事情
different things they can work with
他们可以合作的不同事物
ultra certain things like a long XML
超长的东西，例如长XML
documents neo4j result sets jdbc
文档neo4j结果集jdbc
resultset LCIF data TPA JMS matching pet
结果集LCIF数据TPA JMS匹配宠物
stuff etc right so in a flash file CSV
东西等等，所以在Flash文件CSV中
files and messaging hibernate all these
文件和消息传递使所有这些休眠
kinds of item readers and lighters but
各种物品阅读器和打火机，但
there are very common ones especially
特别是很普通的
the domain of - like ABCs and like file
的域-像ABC和文件
system so in this first milestone which
系统，因此在第一个里程碑中
is just the mideast last week there's
只是上周的中东
already support for reading and and
已经支持阅读和
writing their support for builder 8 guys
写他们对建造者8人的支持
- expressing a reader and a writer for
-表达读者和作家的
working with Fox isms and for working
与Fox isms一起工作
with data sources among others and there
与其他地方的数据源
are more on the way as we march towards
我们朝着前进的方向前进
a GME but I and somebody loves to
一个GME，但我和某人喜欢
imagine works with different years and
想象不同年份的作品
super happy to see these builders arise
看到这些建筑商兴起，我感到非常高兴
because spring Bansha is a fairly old
因为春天的长沙是一个相当老的
swing PARCC assessment projects go it's
开展PARCC评估项目
been around since 2006
自2006年以来
it's co-developed by spring team and I
它是由Spring团队和我共同开发的
think it's a venture and that that work
认为这是一项冒险并且可以成功
was born out of you know customers who
是由您而生的，您知道客户是谁
had use cases related to moving and
有与搬家有关的用例，
migrating back chuckles so it's been
迁移回轻笑，所以一直
used by some of the biggest than the
比某些人使用的最大
best earning in the world we're trying
我们正在尝试的世界上最好的收入
to solve these kind of vast workload
解决这类繁重的工作
problems and so it's very full of
问题，所以它充满了
perfect spin it's very stable but it
完美旋转，它非常稳定，但是
also can also the time and the xml
也可以把时间和xml
configuration format for for spring was
弹簧的配置格式为
prevalent and it's good the only way to
流行，这是唯一的好方法
go in recent years there's been a java
近年来出现了Java
configuration api in terms of the job
根据工作配置api
builder factory in that set builder
那个建造者中的建造者工厂
faculty approaches and our java
教师方法和我们的java
configuration all that stuff if we added
配置所有这些东西，如果我们添加
me some ears but one thing that remained
我有些耳朵，但剩下的一件事
very much oriented towards the xml
非常面向xml
configuration where you would specify
您将在其中指定的配置
lots of different properties on a beam
光束上有许多不同的特性
or these various item rated item writers
或这些不同的项目评级项目作者
which meant that each time i want to
这意味着我每次想
define a matter meter by madam
夫人定义一个物质计量表
I'd have to say set this set that says
我不得不说设置这集说
that you know etc and it gets a little
你知道等等，它会有点
overwhelming so now it's very nice to
压倒性的所以现在很高兴
have these convenience builders so let's
有这些便利设施制造商，所以让我们
see you the first thing we need is a
看到你，我们需要的第一件事是
flat file item reader of type person
人型平面文件项目阅读器
we're going to call us a file reader and
我们将称我们为文件阅读器，
we're going to use the flat file item
我们将使用平面文件项
reader builder and that comes in that
读者生成器
comes in spring batch for that oh so we
春天来了，所以我们
need to specify that we want our spring
需要指定我们想要春天
project to use that version for 900 M 1
项目将该版本用于900 M 1
and do the default one right so here
并执行默认的默认设置，所以在这里
we're overriding the default spring boot
我们将覆盖默认的Spring Boot
imported spring batch generation right
进口弹簧批生产权
so there we are there's our flat file
所以我们有平面文件
item reader let's specify a few things
项目阅读器让我们指定一些东西
the first thing we need to specify the
首先，我们需要指定
name so it's going to be a file leader
名称，因此它将成为文件负责人
and the second thing when you discuss
当你讨论第二件事
apply as the resource with what data are
以什么数据作为资源申请
we reading that you want to read data
我们阅读您想阅读的数据
from the file system a CSV file that
从文件系统的CSV文件中
you've seen on the console here inside
您已经在里面的控制台上看到了
we need to subsidize what that we don't
我们需要补贴我们不想要的
see it I'm going to have it be a
看到它，我将要成为一个
parameter of inputs which will be
输入参数将是
provided into the print your application
提供给您的应用程序打印
right so input this is a screen for amic
正确，所以输入这是amic屏幕
abstraction a resource of spring/summer
提取春季/夏季的资源
core ILO resource and so as you know in
国际劳工组织的核心资源，正如您所知
spring there's all men are different
春天，所有人都不同
resources and communications for
资源和通讯
different things so in definitions FAT
FAT中的定义不同
FAT file system DFS URLs past we have
过去的FAT文件系统DFS URL
their fun Java instance on so a lot of
他们有趣的Java实例
Java and I know rather lots of different
Java和我知道很多不同
um good options here or didn't matter
在这里很好的选择还是没关系
which one you use you can specify that
您可以使用哪一个来指定
into a glass of grabbing the screen
到玻璃抓屏
reader for you so here we've always got
为您准备的阅读器，所以在这里我们总是有
a a flat file item we don't want to map
我们不想映射的平面文件项
it to a CMS audio type person and I want
交给CMS音频类型的人，我想要
to read the data that is submitted by
读取提交的数据
comma and that has columns like the
逗号，并且具有像
column bar the first name is H and the
列栏的名字是H，
email will place first name
电子邮件将放置名字
age and renal cancer and then you should
年龄和肾癌，那么你应该
have emanated between our clinic section
已经在我们的诊所之间发出
light office all SSI data set and such
轻办公室的所有SSI数据集等
so there's our flat file as a meter
所以我们的平面文件是米
that'll be able to make it provided or
就能提供它或
inject it into the screen definition
将其注入屏幕定义
here now we need be anybody writer liver
现在我们需要成为任何人的作家肝脏
jbp right if I wanna say KBC sash items
jbp对，如果我想说KBC腰带项目
liner of type person DC writer and this
型人DC作家的划线员和这个
is before when you take advantage of the
在您利用优势之前
Builder instead of a lot of
生成器，而不是很多
configuration itself of cells and so
配置细胞本身等等
we'll think bring in the person and
我们会考虑引进这个人
we're going to tell it to you the data
我们将告诉您数据
source in this case the data sources so
在这种情况下，数据源是这样
on the passivity book keeps figure for
被动书上的数字
us based on these books five properly so
我们根据这些书五本适当地
I'm going to connect into my people
我将与我的人建立联系
allies it expect we're going to use a
它期望我们将使用一个盟友
sequence and or less like research into
顺序或类似研究
people's at the table epidemic going to
人们在餐桌上流行
create age first name you know values H
创建年龄的名字，你知道值H
first name email and the then you need
名电子邮件，然后您需要
to run tell it once helped swing batches
告诉它曾经帮助批量生产
to use the field on the folder that's
使用以下文件夹中的字段
coming from the reader so whenever the
来自读者，所以无论何时
readers going to leave the data from the
读者将要离开
fascism and turn it into a photo effects
法西斯主义并将其变成照片效果
person that's going to be then passed to
然后将要传递给的人
the writer which we going to expensive
我们要昂贵的作家
property because it focuses those slices
属性，因为它集中了这些切片
you map in there and use as a result of
您在其中进行映射，并由于
primer for the sequencing idea here
这里的测序思路入门
compared to Satan's planner so there's
与撒旦的计划者相比，
that we also want to provide a
我们也想提供一个
well I can exist assault before need for
好吧，我可以在需要之前存在攻击
this that should be enough we're using
这就是我们正在使用的足够了
Athena for so spring batch will create a
雅典娜的春季拍卖会
means of travel or gbq sentence based on
基于的旅行方式或gbq句子
that data source for intrinsically
该数据源本质上
although have the option to to override
尽管可以选择覆盖
that you want to now we need to plug
您想要现在我们需要插入
this all in and make sure it's working
所有这一切，并确保它正常工作
it's going to expect a input parameter
它会期待一个输入参数
so for a little prototyping here let's
所以在这里做一些原型制作
just hard code in there and conduct set
只是其中的硬代码并进行设置
properties input and then we'll commit
属性输入，然后我们提交
to these users say long sex off in dot
对这些用户说，长时间性交
CSV let's get up this path and again
CSV让我们一次又一次地走这条路
this is using the special URL context
这是使用特殊的URL上下文
for spring Windows abstraction so it's
对于春季Windows抽象，所以
like that later on we're going to have
这样以后我们将有
an output CSU so you should go ahead and
输出CSU，所以您应该继续
specify that here well there's our input
指定这里很好，这是我们的输入
notebook and we will turn those into
笔记本，我们将把它们变成
properties that can be injected involved
可以注入的属性
in the values even assign lamentation
在值甚至分配感叹
that should work that should be very
应该工作，应该非常
simple example of course if you need to
当然简单的例子，如果您需要
make sure that you have data that you
确保您拥有自己的数据
have database so let's go ahead to our
有数据库，让我们继续前进
resources director here and create a new
资源总监在这里创建一个新的
file
文件
so we call it C months at sea school and
所以我们在海上学校称之为C个月
in forgot table of people if exist
在被遗忘的人表中（如果存在）
people we're going to configure data
我们要配置数据的人
sources or a teacher time of interacting
来源或老师互动的时间
with our database every builder maybe
使用我们的数据库，每个建造者
the batch database graduated that
批处理数据库毕业了
bastard let's test the connection here
混蛋让我们在这里测试连接
good all right apply now we can
好吧，现在就申请，我们可以
interrogate it and goes and see let's
审问它，去看看我们
not talk table people good and when I
不说表人好，当我
want to create a table that is really
想要创建一个真正的表
hit on every one of a table people ID
击中每个桌子人ID
big homes lot smaller on ice Oh
大房子在冰上小很多哦
and most people this is that as our
和大多数人一样，这是我们的
first feels we want another one for the
首先感觉我们想要另一个
email in effect email on our two five
通过电子邮件发送有关我们的两个五个邮件
five not know okay an Olympic age of in
五不知道还可以进入奥林匹克时代
lemon Modena even more enough not know
柠檬摩德纳甚至更多，不知道
on the curse name on our coupon
在优惠券上的诅咒名字上
not know okay so there's our simple GDL
不知道好吧，所以我们有简单的GDL
then you drop the table on every start
然后在每次开始时都放下桌子
for this convention is even a sequins if
这个约定甚至是一个亮片，如果
we had option is excited specified of
我们有选择激动的指定
theta dot equal to CC to file we're
等于CC的theta点归档
going to be read by screen 1860 to be
将由屏幕1860读取
super book this is not the simplest
超级书，这不是最简单的
ambassadors different convenient vistas
大使不同的方便远景
because we can have swing install our
因为我们可以摆动安装我们的
table persons and it connects to the
表人员，它连接到
data store so that means everyone have
数据存储，这意味着每个人都有
to worry about that being present so
担心存在
let's see if everything goes to plan we
让我们看看一切是否按计划进行
should be able to run this and then
应该能够运行此，然后
visit the accomplice
探亲
and so that's all from c-section work
这都是剖腹产的
okay looks like it okay maybe something
好的看起来像这样，也许有些东西
along the table back really does okay
沿着桌子后面真的很好
but we don't see the data reflected in
但我们看不到数据反映在
the output I wonder why so I've been
输出，我想知道为什么会这样
thinking supply and we're ordering
考虑供应，我们正在订购
constructor for the person poacher which
偷猎者的建设者
is what thing is going to map to the
将会映射到什么
record try sir
记录尝试先生
here we go
开始了
else's on incopy is not sizable Felisa
其他人在副本上的规模不大Felisa
spices better in France again it's about
香料在法国再好一点了
without children let's Lambada
没有孩子，我们来Lambada
nothing like compliments calling it dead
赞不绝口
simple to get past ok let's give the
简单的过去吧，让我们给
remote function direct so let's see
远程功能直接，让我们看看
really hyper okay we've got together for
真的超级好吧，我们在一起
age you know I do this bit has been
你知道我做这个的年龄
written to the day wait that's fine
写到当天的等待，这很好
now I want to see you know I want to see
现在我想见你知道我想见
the distribution I want to see how many
我想看看分布
people have a certain image sizes ten
人们有一定的图像尺寸十
thousand records so we're going to do a
千条记录，所以我们要做一个
very simple query and then we'll write
非常简单的查询，然后我们将编写
that resulting data out to another CSV
产生的数据输出到另一个CSV
file so we're going to do the same kind
文件，所以我们将做同样的事情
of thing in Reverse this is a single
在逆向中这是一个单一的
step you can have multiple steps and
步骤可以有多个步骤，
then that is the way you connect this
那就是你连接这个的方式
stuff is just an X and then provide
东西只是一个X然后提供
another step now of course you can also
现在再走一步，您当然也可以
say on and then apply a pattern that
说，然后应用一个模式
matches the status of the completed
匹配完成状态
previous step of a previous stage myself
我自己上一个阶段的上一步
you've done the content here you can see
您已经完成了这里的内容，您可以看到
but the job itself has a completed seven
但是工作本身已经完成了七个
like on the each step also can return
就像每一步也可以返回
step Alex think that's totally expecting
亚历克斯（Alex）认为那完全是期待
to use this sort of quick workflow you
要使用这种快速的工作流程
can do also it's really cool workflow
也可以做到，这真的很酷
kind of things our jobs
我们工作的事情
sort of flow decisions and even the
各种流量决策，甚至
ability to provide a custom object that
提供自定义对象的能力
makes the decisions problematic right so
使决策成为问题，所以
but but for our purposes it's simple
但出于我们的目的，这很简单
enough to just leave it like this just
足以像这样离开它
have a steps that one before the other
有一个步骤，一个在另一个之前
another thing instead of having am a
另一件事而不是成为
step up steps instead of only step up
加强步骤，而不只是加强
set the rather instead having a subset
设置而不是有一个子集
of has a leader in the writer your steps
在作家中拥有领导者
can also you can also use something
也可以用一些东西
called a tactic an attack that is a
称为战术是一种攻击
certain generic
某些通用
fall through mechanisms it's not because
跌倒机制不是因为
you can put in the middle of your
你可以把你的中间
clothes immer and it can be used to be
浸入衣服，它可以用来
something that easy strictly speaking an
严格来讲，这很容易
item leader or not mitre I also should
项目负责人或不斜切我也应该
mention that you have a third type of
提到你有第三种类型的
office here called a food centers now a
现在这里的办公室叫做食品中心
processor is very simple this eventually
处理器很简单，这最终
on this case is where you won the
在这种情况下，您赢得了
classes in spring batch where you would
春季班的课程
provide most of the business on discern
清楚地提供大部分业务
all that may be very useful with any in
所有这些都可能非常有用
fact of default and imposes goes out of
违约和强加于事实
the box yeah all of these are just
盒子，所有这些都只是
wrappers or adapters these are not
包装或适配器这些不是
similar to things or to the repo this is
类似于东西或回购，这是
where you put business logic right so
您将业务逻辑放在正确的位置
the contract here is that you get the
这里的合同是你得到
person that came out of the reader and
来自读者的人
you can do something for that person and
你可以为那个人做些事情，
then that's what gets sent to the
那就是发送到
writers just want to do any kind of
作家只是想做任何一种
enrichment augmentation transformations
浓缩扩增转化
anything you want you can set business
您想要的任何事情都可以开展业务
logic here maybe you want to go through
逻辑在这里，也许你想经历
all the records in a database and do
数据库中的所有记录并执行
some sort of taxa nation women and then
某类国家的妇女，然后
write the results at the Vegas so that
在拉斯维加斯写下结果，以便
could be done as a writer so another day
可以当作家
looks fine in this case we don't need to
在这种情况下看起来不错，我们不需要
climb right so we've got everything we
向右爬，所以我们拥有了一切
need
需要
let's go ahead and go the second step
让我们继续第二步
process f2 SBS park it and then the
处理f2 SBS将其停放，然后
theorem say CDs to file by sending
定理说CD通过发送来归档
everything before but in Reverse
除反向以外的所有内容
and what we're going to do is we're
而我们要做的是
going to flip all from the people table
要从人员表中翻转全部
and like a count and then we age and
像伯爵，然后我们变老，
improve it by being sure we'll get a and
通过确保我们会得到a和
mapping of age to how many people have
年龄与多少人的对应关系
that me now looking expresses in terms
我现在正在寻找表达
of a map of integer like will be a Kiwi
像整数的地图将是一个猕猴桃
will be the age and the value will be BF
将为年龄，值为BF
yeah
是的
count of that age and so we're
那个年龄的数字，所以我们
specifying map integer integer twice
指定映射整数两次
chunk I'm going to do the same chunk
我将做相同的块
size there bring in the map type where
那里的大小带来地图类型
we are you can specify a reader and the
我们可以为您指定读者，并且
writer
作家
254 and this gets us into a bit of a
254，这使我们陷入了困境
problem doesn't it we've got an item
问题不是，我们有一个项目
reader in my item right up here and we
读者在我这里的物品中，我们
haven't really been raised as a lot of
并没有真正提高
type I could have found cast them to the
我本来可以找到的类型
specific type
具体类型
you know wouldn't do all of us do with
你知道我们不会一起做
all that much good because you know
一切都很好，因为你知道
eventually in a complicated application
最终在复杂的应用程序中
you very well may have most instances of
您可能会遇到大多数情况
a flat file item reader or a BBC match
平面文件项目阅读器或BBC比赛
item writer for example so you need
例如项目作家，所以您需要
types disambiguation alone you think I'm
单单消除歧义，你以为我是
a quite fit you know you could use a
非常适合，您知道您可以使用
qualifier you could say this is a views
预选赛你可以说这是一个看法
convention based on the names of the
基于名称的约定
method or the being rather since the
方法或存在，因为
name of the method or the name of being
方法的名称或存在的名称
okay and whether if it's a sewer step
好的，是否是下水道步骤
one are one that everyone's but but that
每个人都是一个，但是那个
old it's a kind of genius one thing I
老是我的天才
like to do is use sort of configuration
喜欢做的是使用某种配置
classes I like to have a kind of a
我喜欢上一门课
wrapper configuration class for each
每个包装器配置类
step like a public static class
像公共静态类一样走
step one configuration and this is to
第一步配置，这是为了
say message configuration class that in
说说消息配置类
turn contains two beam definitions and
转弯包含两个光束定义，
it's a you get a free kind of scoping
这是一种免费的范围界定
for this place the benefit is that now
对于这个地方，好处是现在
instead of me injecting these two beams
而不是我注入这两个光束
that I need directions I can say except
我需要我可以说的指示，除了
for one configuration of one config and
对于一种配置的一种配置
I can just be reckoned 15 definition so
我只能算出15个定义，所以
record time so this is a natural thing
记录时间，这是自然的事情
to do in spring or it is we're saying I
在春天做，还是说我
want to inject the configuration class
要注入配置类
itself as IB and then I want to have
本身就是IB，然后我想拥有
access to the beans that are created
访问创建的bean
from those configurations provider
从那些配置提供者
method but make make them stick we're
方法，但使他们坚持我们
not actually calling the method reforms
并未真正要求进行方法改革
going to give us a return value you can
给我们一个返回值，你可以
do the same thing you know from one beam
从一束光做同样的事情
to another if I want to have my file
如果我想拥有我的文件
reader call you know the screen here I
读者打电话给你，我知道这里的屏幕
decide calls 311
决定通话311
there's no reason I couldn't just say
没有理由我不能只说
this that food and then use it that feed
这个食物，然后用它来喂养
but said being will go through the
但说存在会经历
lifecycle and all the initialization
生命周期和所有初始化
callbacks and all except that spring
回调以及除春季以外的所有回调
guaranteed and it would also be a
保证，这也将是
singleton so I could call this fermented
单身，所以我可以称之为发酵
this X is a thousand times and I go only
这个X是一千次，我只去
ever have but a false in there like one
曾经有过但只有一个虚假的像
beep so we're doing the same thing here
哔哔声，所以我们在这里做同样的事情
but we're calling in sea beans so
但是我们打电话给豆子
dereferencing your beans on the
取消引用您的bean
configuration type of cell
单元的配置类型
so this is going to require a exception
所以这将需要一个例外
it costs of going to show that and you
证明这一点的成本，而你
know that didn't myself scoping through
知道那不是我自己的范围
a little bit of isolation so now we can
有点孤立，所以现在我们可以
define another configuration fast for
快速定义另一个配置
step two so as configuration public
第二步，以便配置公共
static class status class
静态类状态类
step three configuration and we are
第三步配置，我们
going to describe first and foremost a a
首先要描述aa
babyish reason so let's say item later
幼稚的原因，让我们稍后再说
map of in figure consider Oh KBC meters
图中的地图考虑哦KBC米
the turn music jvc cursor item meter but
转音乐jvc光标项目米，但
of course we're not going to use the
当然，我们不会使用
course our leaders are going to use a
当然，我们的领导者将使用
builder to build that item students I'm
建造那个学生的建造者
going to return data in terms of its
将要根据其返回数据
meaning a map as a tuple here so we're
表示地图为元组，所以我们
going to need data source of course and
当然需要数据源
so spring our data source and we'll get
所以春天我们的数据源，我们将得到
a name so I'm going to say up to speed
一个名字，所以我要跟你说
on the then we'll map the data that
然后我们将映射数据
comes back so we're going to provide a
回来，所以我们将提供一个
new spring morning's a lot of Rome a
新春天的早晨，罗马很多
part this is very similar if anybody
如果有人的话，这非常相似
ever use the GBC templates in spring
曾经在春季使用GBC模板
very much properly in Ramsey's container
非常正确地放在拉姆齐的容器中
to stay one like the Davis kind of
保持像戴维斯这样的人
further talking the contract is very
再说合同很
simple says when the swing match
简单地说，当挥杆比赛
component the leader may be a record
领导者可能是记录的组成部分
into so if moving so the record is going
因此，如果移动，记录将继续
to ask us to map a result set into
要求我们将结果集映射到
something meaningful in this case a map
在这种情况下有意义的地图
of an in your just life so keep is
在你的正义生活中，所以保持
always a return costume box single can
总是回程服装盒单罐
map on the data is going to be a result
在数据上映射将是结果
set shot get in and so the a for the age
定点进入，所以这个年龄段
and we'll set just in C for the
我们将只在C中设置
challenge
挑战
now this of course is a nice lambda for
现在这当然是一个很好的lambda
the Lambo okay use that we are missing
我们错过的兰博好用
something out when you sold it right
当你把它正确卖掉时
after that that build that should work
在那之后那个应该工作的构建
and should give us our data it's going
并应向我们提供数据
to map it into that and then we need for
映射到那个，然后我们需要
the reader now we need to wait - did I
读者现在我们需要等待-我是否
think that was open data and then write
以为是开放数据然后写
it out to the filesystem Franco and only
将其发送到文件系统Franco，仅
the sequel thing of course I can
我当然可以续集
certainly the sequel statements arrived
续集声明肯定到了
at that computer calculated for my face
在为我的脸计算的那台计算机上
one count aged from our cast HP on page
第1页的“从我们施放的HP变老”
a some people food five ink area so
一些人的食物五个墨水区
that's that'll be SS Monica to the feed
这就是供稿的SS Monica
will be an account age a will be a force
将是帐户年龄，将是一支力量
it will turn that into a map a singleton
它将单身变成地图
Mathis as one records one entry so is
Mathis作为一个记录一个条目，所以
that it can suck either way in it and
它可以吸入其中的任何一种方式
that's ours our reader down to the air
这是我们的读者
writers of them click item writer or a
他们的作者单击项目作家或
map of integer compressed file lighter
整数压缩文件打火机的映射
and same idea we're going to write out
同样的想法我们要写出来
to a file confirm solicitors provide an
确认律师提供了文件
output and if you reference our data
输出，如果您引用我们的数据
studio office Crowder here and there was
工作室办公室Crowder在这里和那里
a new flat file item lighter builder own
一个新的平面文件项目打火机建造者拥有
map all integer integer click build and
映射所有整数，整数，单击生成和
going to provide this a name those file
将为其提供名称的那些文件
lighter
打火机
the name value a leaf we can get these
名称值一片叶子，我们可以得到这些
components are going to say to Davis the
组件将对戴维斯说
estate for the progress the progress for
进度的遗产
this job or which days things on the
这份工作或哪一天的事情
Davis so one of the checkpoints to go to
戴维斯所以要去的检查站之一
look at the database until we've got so
看看数据库，直到我们知道了
far right so we need to give a name we
最右边的，所以我们需要给我们起个名字
can use generic name to go on but it
可以使用通用名称继续
helps me just a little descriptive
帮我一点描述
I'm being serious okay here and what is
我说的很认真，这是什么
the file writer when the context of this
文件编写器时的上下文
job is pretty clear but give enough jobs
工作很明确，但要提供足够的工作
you may want to get some more inventive
您可能想获得更多创新
we do that so we just want to that
我们这样做，所以我们只想
resource that we just described and we
我们刚刚描述的资源，我们
need to provide a line exit now the line
需要提供行出口，现在行
aggregators job except this is to figure
聚合器工作，除了要计算
out how to take the input data that's
找出如何获取输入数据
coming in from the FOSDEM and turn that
从FOSDEM进入
into a set of Records that's you know
进入一组记录，您知道
looking money or whether it's going to
看钱还是去
take the data coming in from the jbq
接收来自jbq的数据
reader in turn that into record secondly
读者依次将其记录
it's not due to the Foxton as our mind
这不是因为我们的思维
so it's our job to turn these three
所以把这三个变成我们的工作
objects instead of strings alternate
对象而不是字符串交替
right but you don't have to do most of
是的，但是您不必做大多数
that work that you lose this delimited
你失去这个定界的工作
line I was going so we need to apply
我要去的路线，所以我们需要申请
this limiter I think the default is is
这个限制器，我认为默认值为
comma or another yeah comment anyway but
无论如何，逗号或其他评论
never never to be explicit and then we
永远永远不要明确，然后我们
can provide a new field extract ensign
可以提供一个新的字段提取标志
or field extractor and the contract here
或现场提取器和合同在这里
is clearly just going forward like even
显然只是像
a map which is the input from the reader
读者输入的地图
it turns and a an array of values that
它会旋转，并生成一个值数组
can be done using to dampen space right
可以用来减轻空间
so let's replace that will say integer
所以我们将其替换为整数
mops max and reset all in rid of that
清除最大并重置所有内容
next it was only one value ever
接下来，这只是一个价值
this is a static space candle and what
这是一个静态太空蜡烛，什么
we're going to do let's say I'm next on
我们要说的是我下一步
get key let's it's valid right so I
得到钥匙，让我们他妈的这是正确的权利，所以我
want to write the the Vanessa column
想写Vanessa专栏
will be VL the temp the right values
将是VL温度的正确值
right column wzl rather than less value
右列wzl而不是更少的值
will be doing age like fine will make us
会像美好的年龄一样使我们
account and I think not ought to do it
帐户，我认为不应该这样做
if I leave is enough here you can so
如果我离开这里就足够了
fine coding the header for example had a
精细编码标题，例如有一个
manager work with the header should
经理与标题一起工作
things we deleted the XMP if it exists
如果存在，我们删除了XMP
and all this kind of stuff should we
所有这些东西我们应该
append to the file of course of writing
附加到写作过程中
out for that new file so all this is
拿出那个新文件，所以这就是
such a good fly but I think for our
这样的苍蝇，但我认为对于我们
purposes it will be fine to leave things
目的就可以了
out they are so here we go we found our
出来，所以我们在这里，我们找到了我们的
step two configurations event TV series
第二步配置事件电视连续剧
in a file writer and we can do the same
在文件编写器中，我们可以做同样的事情
damages here to configuration
此处损坏配置
and you know that impacting eknoll again
你知道那再次影响着eknoll
these don't contribute to the equation
这些对方程没有帮助
of the objects they're just telling
他们刚刚告诉的对象
spring to column method it doesn't care
弹簧色谱柱方法，它不在乎
about the parameters that we pass in
关于我们传入的参数
because it's already got that feed and
因为它已经有了提要
so this is it's all just you don't have
所以这就是你所没有的
to provide the parameters we're going to
提供我们将要使用的参数
provided whether its dependence
提供是否依赖
injection container itself later on or
注射容器本身稍后或
tops earlier on in this case because
在这种情况下排在前面，因为
they're singleton still have already
他们仍然是单身
been initialized alright so that I think
已经初始化好了，所以我认为
should do it elite if now if everything
如果现在一切都应该精英做
goes correctly you should be able to see
正确进行，您应该能够看到
on the faucets in here outlook those are
在这里的水龙头上，这些是
out Sofia let's go ahead and run this
索非亚出去吧，让我们继续运行
it's alright LC and there we are
好的LC，我们在那里
unless we have the age and on the right
除非我们有年龄并且在右边
graphics the number of observed
图形观察的数量
instances okay so it says here that the
实例还可以，所以它在这里说
age 99 was you know under day time in
你是在白天知道99岁吗
that in that in good 5 or index.php
在那好5或index.php
breakfast 99 for you cm NFL under length
早餐99厘米以下为您提供的NFL
in racket so it lines up with what would
在球拍中，所以它会与
expect now this is a simple example we
现在期望这是一个简单的例子，我们
we another swing batch will do the right
我们另一个摇摆批次将做对
thing in terms of chunking it will go
就分块而言，它会走
through the data and leave so much and
通过数据，留下了很多，
then write out in a chunk that is that
然后以大块写出来
data to there could be out the writer
那里的数据可能是作者
and this is this means that they are
这就是说他们是
code will work it won't it won't load to
代码会正常工作，不会加载到
updated members more in Atlanta and all
更新了更多亚特兰大及所有地区的成员
the item readers animators are geared to
该项目的读者动画师适应
want to file by the contract for an item
想要按合同提交项目
writer is to take a list of n items
作者要列出n个项目
which is an only child size or less and
小于或等于一个孩子的大小，并且
then write them out matchbox them is by
然后把它们写出火柴盒
definition one of the things that you
定义你要做的一件事
don't want to have to do yourself is it
不想自己做就是
then the art of seeing works large
然后看艺术就大了
amounts of data such that if there's a
大量的数据，如果有
bug in your processing code you won't
处理代码中的错误，您不会
find it and so maybe our so I'm fast
找到它，也许我们这么快
jobs could run for 24 hours there's no
作业可以运行24小时，没有
reason a batch job couldn't take hours
为什么批处理工作不会花费数小时
and hours and hours or all night for
和几个小时或几个小时或整夜
some time fine so you want to use many
好的时间，所以你想用很多
of these sort of batteries that are
这类电池中
included spring that as possible
包括尽可能的春天
being young any important that we've
年轻一点，我们已经重要
just shown here leave the building a
刚刚显示在这里离开建筑物
simple job is just the beginning right
简单的工作仅仅是开始
in an earlier spring tip we look at
在较早的春季技巧中，我们来看
twink lab data flow you can actually
实际上，您可以轻松获得实验室数据流
orchestrate batch jobs you can clean
编排可以清理的批处理作业
contact on stink cloud dataflow so that
联系臭云数据流，以便
is the subject for another video I think
是我认为另一部影片的主题
but this should give you a quick
但这应该可以让您快速
introduction quick look at swing batch
简介快速查看秋千批次
what you should appreciate is an
您应该欣赏的是
instance use the handle sort of finite
实例使用有限的句柄
workload or clothes that have a
工作量或衣服
beginning in them end and a lot of data
从他们开始到结束，大量数据
is still very much fit in that world but
仍然非常适合那个世界，但是
a lot of things are also
很多东西也
infinite weather is a never-ending for
无限的天气是永无止境的
this there's that the capability that
这就是那种能力
you find in springtime data flow so if
您会在春季数据流中找到
you look at when conveyance or it is a
你看什么时候运输或它是一个
amalgamation or a mix of both the batch
合并或两者的混合
puts things of support here and spring
在春天给这里提供支持
match and the event-driven sort of
比赛和事件驱动的
infinite and never-ending stream of
无穷无尽的
events support that you get from
您从中获得的事件支持
innovation it brings and brings together
它带来并汇集在一起​​的创新
both worlds and makes it as easy as
两全其美，并使其像
possible to describe solutions no matter
无论如何都可以描述解决方案
what the nature of that solution all
该解决方案的本质是什么
right well this has been a quick look at
好吧，这是快速浏览
spring batch we'll see you in next video
春季批，我们将在下一个视频中见
thanks for watching
谢谢收看
you
您